ED]
℃-ute
Good morning.
Is that your name today?
Today is Osaka.
Please share your enthusiasm.
Enthusiasm?
What's that?
What is it?
Huh?
Mmm-hmm.
Let's go up and see what kind of subject we can get.
What? Why the helo?
Hmm.
Why the heck not?
Erotic. This color reminds me of Helo.
Why?
Maybe it's a little bit obvious.
It looks like Helo, doesn't it?
It's a Heero color.
Cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha-cha.
Oh, please eat quickly.
Let me dance.
Why?
Please.
I'm Maimi Sakurabee. Please.
I'm Sakurai Rizmar Capper.
Please.
That's all I'm asking you to be aware of.
Yes, I'm Maimi Sakurai.
I liked the new song.
Thank you for doing it.
Thank you very much.
The lame one is in the show.
Can I have the second one now?
But you ate it, Yuna.
I'll eat it.
It was delicious.
Where are we?
Osaka!
We are
ABC!
Kaka!
Yuko!
Ebitu!
Mai ko!
Nikko, avec Maiko!
Nervous.
I'm nervous.
Oh, I'm really nervous.
Nervous.
I'll do my best.
How did it go?
I'm nervous.
It's been a while, so I'm really nervous.
You can tell.
It's started.
Congratulations.
How was our chi? It's nice to be able to say that to each other all the time and keep it up.
# Offerings I feel like I can fight for you
# I'll still love you after ten years, you and me
Because I'm lucky to have met you here and now
And more than that, it's an endearment.
So we can hang on just a little bit longer
Let's say that one word together
You have nothing to be ashamed of
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
How about you?
I'm good. I'm good.
Good.
It's good. It's good.
All right.
Thank you for your time.
We are.
I started this earlier, but I'm going to send you to the Gotoh family at the famous school, and I'm going to send you to various regions,
I'm going to dress in the image of the Gotoh family there, because I like clothes a lot,
Since I love clothes so much, I thought I would try to dress in the image of the Gotoh family, and I'm doing well.
Today, I imagined Glico in the image of Osaka,
I imagined Glico.
This is it, isn't it?